If they hear you, they hunt you.
A Quiet Place is a horror, drama, science fiction
film directed by John Krasinski.
A family is forced to live in silence while hiding
from creatures that hunt by sound.
Evelyn Abbott, played by Emily Blunt.
Lee Abbott, played by John Krasinski.
Regan Abbott, played by Millicent Simmonds.
Marcus Abbott, played by Noah Jupe.
Beau Abbott, played by Cade Woodward.
Man in the Woods, played by Leon Russom.
A Quiet Place is an American apocalyptic and post-apocalyptic horror film series set in a world
inhabited by blind extraterrestrial creatures with a heightened sense of hearing.
The story was conceived of by Scott Beck and Bryan Woods.
The first film in the series, A Quiet Place (2018), and its sequel A
Quiet Place Part II (2020), were directed by John Krasinski.
The third film, the spinoff prequel A Quiet Place: Day One
(2024), was directed by Michael Sarnoski.
The three films have a combined gross of over $900
million at the worldwide box office.
A video game based on the series, A Quiet Place: The Road Ahead, was developed by
Stormind Games and published by Saber Interactive on October 17, 2024.
A comic series, A Quiet Place: Storm Warning, published by IDW
Publishing, is set to begin releasing on March 11, 2026.
The film explores themes of pregnancy, fireworks, deaf,
post-apocalyptic future, alien life-form.
The tone is dark and thought_provoking and emotional.